<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>KnowledgeZero</title>
  
  
  <link href="https://www.knowledgezero.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://www.knowledgezero.com/"/>
  <updated>2021-02-09T18:07:22.207Z</updated>
  <id>https://www.knowledgezero.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>The Science Club</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Act II - No Country for Practical Men</title>
    <link href="https://www.knowledgezero.com/no-country-for-practical-men/"/>
    <id>https://www.knowledgezero.com/no-country-for-practical-men/</id>
    <published>2021-02-09T00:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-02-09T18:07:22.207Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="./electric-sheep.png"></p><p>It’s decided, we set sail! We leave our “Salem’s Lot”. The boat journey is long and one sleepless night we can’t stop thinking about the practical observations of the practical experts: “The problem with cyberINsecure animals is that they are easily attacked by fungi, viruses, and many others; often leading to the death of the animal. Observations show that the attack pattern is as follows. Fungi move over the body of the animal (behavior called information gathering) until they find a weak spot and corrode the skin (creating an entry point). Viruses are then free to exploit the weak spot and enter the animal, reading the plain-DNA and exploiting it for their replication. The only solution is to give a great dose of anti-fungi and anti-viruses every day as a precaution to every animal”. He <em>even</em> concluded by saying: “Viruses are always evolving, and anti-viruses too; but it’s always too late to cure all the cases. We must get faster in reacting to viruses!”. </p><p>And we finally fall asleep. </p><h2 id="The-Im-Practical-God"><a href="#The-Im-Practical-God" class="headerlink" title="The Im-Practical God"></a>The Im-Practical God</h2><p>A dream? We see a God dividing a giant pyramid into pieces of different geometrical shapes: cubes, smaller pyramids, … We slightly turn and we see another God who is shaking his 8-ball whispering: “how much fuel do I need to reach the moon?”.  </p><p>… practical Gods! They too understand by induction from experience?! But Gods do not obey to the rule of experience, the rules of nature, why are they doing it? And why do they all have an ML tag on their forehead? </p><p>We wake up! We must think something up! Our plan is simple: once we have an idea of what a cybersecure animal is, we’ll start empirically testing its correctness. So, we lay down again and, when we close our eyes, we are alone in a colorless, soundless, potentially infinite, <em>space</em>.  </p><p>If there’s a <strong>fact</strong> we can be sure about, is that <em>everything</em> we can think of can somehow be represented in this <strong>space</strong>; cybersecure animals won’t make an exception. Well, to be honest, sometimes we are uncertain if we <strong>know</strong> the truth about something, but we still <strong>believe</strong> it in that space. And to be absolutely honest, this space is no soundless at all, we hear our thoughts and reasoning, we <strong>say</strong> them. This reminds us of a too-simple idea that <a href="https://v-research.github.io/a-free-preface/">every animal, we too, can be conceptualized as thinking subjects who assert their beliefs to anyone who hears</a>, and the facts (of the world around us) will be used to judge the validity of our beliefs. </p><p><img src="./abf.png"></p><p>We hear the captain yelling. We just docked at the port. Where are we? </p><h2 id="The-Model-based-designed-animals-Island"><a href="#The-Model-based-designed-animals-Island" class="headerlink" title="The Model-based-designed-animals Island"></a>The Model-based-designed-animals Island</h2><p><em>Captain</em> We have practical things to do. You, impractical sailor, come back in two weeks! </p><p>So, we head inland, we look up and a forest awaits us. Refreshed, in the forest, we walk upstream along a small brook. We find what seems like an abandoned farm. We can really use a place to stay for a while. Wait… the farm isn’t abandoned. </p><p><em>Us:</em> Morning. </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> Evening, son! You lost? </p><p><em>Us:</em> yes… evening. Eh… yes. Where are we? </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> That way is Hazelden cit… </p><p><em>Us:</em> No, sorry. I mean… what’s the name of this island? </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> This is Model-based-designed-animals island. </p><p><em>Us:</em> What a weird name! </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> It’s an old name. This island was discovered by a group of scientists and engineers. While staying here, they had to come to terms with the island and became farmers. But they did it their way, designing animals and artificially implementing them from the designs. It was beautiful and, after a while, all the animals were artificially engineered. But the cost of living has made us farmers stop designing animals in favor of a much faster “implement and patch” approach. So, we now implement animals without designing them. There’s always something wrong but this is how we discover “new features”… you know?! Plus, we can always patch them. </p><p><em>Us:</em> I see… a bit sad. How about all those new fungi and viruses? </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> That is a tragedy! Practical people are releasing those fungi and viruses to steal or change our animals. </p><p><em>Us:</em> Did you just say, “practical people”? </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> Yes, I still consider myself an architect who designs his animals. The truth is, I’m just as practical as they are. I’m not designing them anymore, just coding, patching, and patching.  </p><p><em>Us:</em> Ever wondered how to design a cybersecure animal? </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> Once we almost did it, but that pig flew away. </p><p>We spent the dinner with the farmer, talking about insecure animals. Basically, any insecure animal he finds is under <strong>attack</strong> by a practical man. Those attacks are exploiting some <strong>vulnerability</strong> of the animal which, in turn, are just <strong>weaknesses</strong> due to <strong>errors</strong> in the farmer’s code. He’s spent decades fixing those errors. Every time he finds one, he fixes it. He even tests his own animals, fixing even more errors. He shared that, at the beginning, new errors popped up every day, but then every hour… until it got unbearable. So, we insist:  </p><p><em>Us:</em> Why don’t you design an animal without errors? </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> I told you already. I did try that, but it wasn’t working properly, and the “secure” animal flew away. </p><p><em>Us:</em> But from your observations, all insecurities can be “cured by” designing an animal without errors. </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> Yes… I tried it with the help of two other farmers: Dolev and Yao. They designed the perfect test. We believed we could identify any insecurity in the logic of our designs. Still, animals were ultimately implemented insecurely. Plus, we invested everything we had… </p><p><em>Us:</em> Wait, you said you could search for insecurities in the logic? How? </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> They identified the actions of viruses and fungi and they came up with this “attacker model” that worked on designs but it… </p><p><em>Us:</em> Ah! That’s the problem! You are testing now, and you were testing back then! An attacker model mimics the attacker but how did you get the idea of the attacker if not from empirical observations? You didn’t design a secure animal; you just tested the design against the idea you had of what an attacker may do. </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> It’s really much more complex that this but, have you got a better idea? </p><p><em>Us:</em> Not really… but your <strong>methodology</strong> seems wrong to me. Just imagine this: what if you couldn’t explain some properties of a real-world triangle. Wouldn’t that suggest that your <strong>idea</strong> of the triangle is somewhat misleading or over-simplifying? I mean… triangles are lines in a one-dimensional space and no area can be understood in that idea(lization). But as soon as you introduce a “better” idea of a triangle in 2D, areas do not just make sense, but can be predicted in the abstract; real-world calculations serve just as confirmation of the accuracy of the predictions. </p><p>We spent the rest of our “vacation” at the farm, mostly studying some of the farmer’s old designs and his animals, asking too many questions, until it was our last night on the island. </p><h2 id="It-Was-a-Dark-and-Stormy-Night"><a href="#It-Was-a-Dark-and-Stormy-Night" class="headerlink" title="It Was a Dark and Stormy Night"></a>It Was a Dark and Stormy Night</h2><p> Already on our boat, we are waiting for better weather conditions. We keep thinking at the days spent with the farmer. We even created our own electric sheep. Kind of weird how it looks like. There’s no mouth, digestion system, smells… It looks like a sheep, but it only has “eyes” and “ears”, an intricate mechanical internal structure, and a low-cost computer in his head. Well, “eyes”… they are not even cameras. One of those “eye” is really just a hole and a light sensitive surface… So simple, and yet we don’t know what a secure eye is… It’s a stupid “port” that the “brain” of the sheep can use to get data from the outer visible world. Light comes to the “eye” and the data encoded in the light is translated and transmitted to the “brain”. </p><p>So, an “eye” just forwards data… and maybe translates data from light into electrical impulses… How bad can that be hacked? Let’s abstract the sheep-eye in our ideal space. </p><p><img src="./sheep-eye.png"></p><p>Here light is correctly translated into electrical impulses and the data carried by the light is equal to the data in the electrical impulses. But what if the eye isn’t working properly? We remember the good Ol’days when math was just <a href="/sets-arent-boxes">boxes</a> (they were called sets, but they were just believed to be boxes). It was so easy, a practical real concept such as a box and its abstract representation as a set were so close that we didn’t really distinguish the two. And yet, we could predict in the abstract all possible configurations of any number of boxes and then test our prediction by building the real-world configuration. We still remember that two boxes can be equal, different, or partially equal. But if we have a box with the light-data of the outside world (the facts) and one the with electric data in the sheep (its beliefs), how can light-data be partially equal to electric data? Well, boxes can be partially overlapping or one into the other. </p><p><img src="./rcc5-boxes.png"></p><p>So Similarly: </p><ul><li>Light-data can be partially translated so that electric-data lacks some data (data partial <strong>delete</strong>). </li><li>Or, vice-versa, light-data lacks some electric-data. So, the eye has <strong>insert</strong>ed some data. </li><li>Or both, and light-data and electric-data overlaps so that some light-data have been <strong>substitute</strong>d with some different electric-data. </li></ul><p>THAT’S IT! We have an abstract ground (made by a space and some operations) that can explain insecure designs… all of them! It was so simple! Any eye can just be secure or insert/remove/substitute data, and nothing else! The adrenaline makes us jump off the bed… but it’s overwhelming, and we faint. A practical god approaches us. </p><p><em>The-Vulnerability-Assessment-Practical-God:</em> Why all this happiness? To me your “idea” is nothing more than an attacker model. </p><p><em>Us:</em> No, it’s not! It’s not the attacker who creates errors, the attacker just uses them. So, we’ve defined every possible behavior with respect to an abstract, general, box-theoretic interpretation… we have an idea and a theory. We can <strong>predict</strong> all the errors that the sheep-eye can make in the abstract, by looking at the configurations of our boxes. Here is how: </p><p><img src="./rcc5-eye.png"></p><p>You see?! We are general because there are no other possible attacks in our abstraction. There are no <em>other</em> possible configurations of those boxes but the ones we described.  </p><p><em>The-Risk-Assessment-Practical-God:</em> AH-AH-AH! You little mortal! You can’t <em>use</em> your “theory”! Can you tell me which one of your configurations will be used to attack? </p><p><em>Us:</em> The fact that an attacker will use one of those configurations or not, isn’t important. It’s just the difference between a potential weakness and an actual vulnerability. But we want to know all the attacks, not just those that attacker discovers or uses. So, we don’t distinguish between errors in the abstract (weaknesses) or errors used in an attack (vulnerability). We want to know all the weaknesses… we’ll think of a metric to prioritize weaknesses which can be used in an attack… one day.  </p><p>We finally wake up and rush off the boat, running to the farm. We wake up the farmer and show him our idea, talking and speculating for a solid hour. He listens carefully, and when we stop… </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> What if you have an eye that, by design, blurs the faces? Its electric-data cannot be expressed in terms of the light-data and your idea won’t be of any use. </p><p><em>Us:</em> … </p><p><em>Farmer:</em> It’s not raining anymore; you have a boat to take. </p><p>He’s right, it stopped raining. The dark and stormy night moved within us. </p><h2 id="UnTrue-Lies"><a href="#UnTrue-Lies" class="headerlink" title="UnTrue Lies"></a>UnTrue Lies</h2><p>For the whole trip back, we did the only thing we could: sailing during the day and detailing our idea during the night; drafting an etiological explanation of the cybersecure animal until we came back home, with our idea ready to be shared. We looked back at our draft and we decided to send it to the farmer with a message: “It’s much more detailed now and there’s much more than what we briefly discussed together. Hope you enjoy it”. His reply? “Thanks”. Maybe he was just too busy to go through it, so we called other farmers and they all replied “thanks”. At first, we thought we just met a lot of busy people but, “thanks” after “thanks”, we started wondering… is there a hidden truth they found in our good-ish approach, so ugly they didn’t dare to tell us? </p><p>And suddenly, an insight! The missing piece of the puzzle! We take a piece of paper and:  </p><blockquote><p>“the internal functioning of the brain of the electric sheep can be seen as a monolithic piece, holding the details of the behavior of the sheep. The first sheep we created was replying “hello world” any time it saw the sun. But that was our dogmatic view! The truth is that it says “hello world” even to a flashlight. The misalignment between what we <strong>require</strong> and what the sheep really does, make us believe in wrong dogmas. Furthermore, the functionality of the sheep is an aggregation of smaller functionalities which we must not dogmatically define but interpret in… &lt;CRACK&gt;“</p></blockquote><p>The pen broke… we must go buy another one. We open the wallet. Is that our last coin?! </p><p><strong>End of Act II</strong></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./electric-sheep.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s decided, we set sail! We leave our “Salem’s Lot”. The boat journey is long and one sleepless</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="cybersecurity" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/cybersecurity/"/>
    
    <category term="cyber-security" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/cyber-security/"/>
    
    <category term="cyber" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/cyber/"/>
    
    <category term="security" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/security/"/>
    
    <category term="sec" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/sec/"/>
    
    <category term="knowledgezero" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/knowledgezero/"/>
    
    <category term="blog" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/blog/"/>
    
    <category term="science" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/science/"/>
    
    <category term="practical-man" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/practical-man/"/>
    
    <category term="philosophy" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/philosophy/"/>
    
    <category term="vulnerability" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/vulnerability/"/>
    
    <category term="risk-assessment" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/risk-assessment/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Act I - Finding Cybersecure</title>
    <link href="https://www.knowledgezero.com/finding-cybersecure/"/>
    <id>https://www.knowledgezero.com/finding-cybersecure/</id>
    <published>2020-12-23T00:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-02-09T18:07:22.207Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="./neon-fish.jpeg" alt="https://www.neon-light.net/proddetail.php?prod=nl-107461-clown-fish-neon-sign"><span class="image-caption">https://www.neon-light.net/proddetail.php?prod=nl-107461-clown-fish-neon-sign</span></p><p>We want to start this journey by asking a simple question: what is a cybersecure (or, simply, secure) system? Some people believe that there exist properties, such as confidentiality, which are necessary conditions for a system to be “secure”. Let us take the case of confidentiality which, when it holds over a piece of information (or a chunk of data), guarantees that information cannot be “understood” but from those who know a certain secret. As an example, if we replace any letter in IBM with the next in the alphabet, we obtain HAL, and only those who know that we’ve used the next letter will be able to understand IBM when they see us writing HAL. Even when a confidentiality algorithm (procedure) is perfect no one would dare to say that it is secure in general, but only insofar security is restricted to confidentiality (confidentiality isn’t sufficient for security). Now, what would change if, instead of confidentiality, we’d consider any other property? What if we say that for a system (or a piece of code) “being reviewed by that guy” is a necessary but not sufficient cybersecurity property? Or what if we say that “having nicely painted blue wires” makes a system secure insofar security is restricted to having nicely painted blue wires? Obviously, they say, not ANY property but SOME specific properties can be considered cybersecurity properties! Interesting… and how do we know which property is a cybersecurity property? Well, that’s the tricky part. </p><h2 id="Once-upon-a-time"><a href="#Once-upon-a-time" class="headerlink" title="Once upon a time"></a>Once upon a time</h2><p>Everything started with the famous CIA-triad and the belief that confidentiality, integrity, and availability could be raised among other properties as glorious cybersecurity properties! It’s obvious, they say, if the great CIA-triad doesn’t hold, a malicious human being could read your messages, alter them, or even prevent you from sending any messages! </p><p>[I know you may be tempted but, please, don’t start chasing other properties or digging into the details of them, it has already been done (from the 70s on).] The desire of listing and detailing these properties is natural, occurs frequently to cybersecurity researchers when left alone in their habitats. You can hear them whispering: “if we knew all of them… it would be just a matter of time before all of our systems become really-really-secure”. The thing is… why after 40 years systems are still insecure? Let’s have a closer look at what we are doing here. </p><h2 id="Honey-I-got-Hacked"><a href="#Honey-I-got-Hacked" class="headerlink" title="Honey, I got Hacked"></a>Honey, I got Hacked</h2><p>One day we wake up and an annoying hacker is altering all the WhatsApp messages we send. Integrity is the property that would make sure no one would be able to mangle with our messages. We pray very hard our oracles and, pufff, integrity it is! But now, something else is happening, we cannot send any message anymore.  </p><p>We are using WhatsApp, we know that when a message is sent it shows a little grayish tick, and while it is sending a message, we get a little grayish clock. Every message we now try to send has a little grayish clock, how is that even possible? Can’t we communicate with WhatsApp anymore? What that heck is that annoying hacker doing now?! The hacker is disrupting the service, we need availability! We thus kneel and pray for availability and once more our prayers are listened to and we see that all our little clocks are now little ticks.  </p><p>Just when we thought our troubles were over, we find out that all our messages are now being published all over the place. They are on Twitter, Pastebin, everywhere. You fool, you forgot about confidentiality. The prayer must be hard this time for the oracles to answer but we don’t give up and eventually we obtain confidentiality. Now things are secure, aren’t they? We got the CIA-triad covered; we must be secured. But this is when something unexpected happens. We get a phone call from Alice, our long-time friend. She’s mad at us for sending that nasty message to her just about 10 seconds ago. But we didn’t send any messages, how is that even possible? Oh no… the hacker is now sending messages and pretends to be us. But how, that’s not possible… we’ve got the CIA-triad, we must be safe and yet, we are not! </p><p>While many people believe the problem is generated by hackers, we believe the problem is the great master beyond any insecurity manifestation: the approach of the practical man! </p><h2 id="The-Practical-Man"><a href="#The-Practical-Man" class="headerlink" title="The Practical Man"></a>The Practical Man</h2><p>This is the approach of the practical man, he who lives his life and then thinks about it, he who finds solutions then problems. Undoubtedly, it takes a lot of effort for the practical man to constantly run in the circle “give me a new cybersecurity issue and I’ll define a cybersecurity property for it”. But that effort is compensated by a HUGE amount of money! A 50+ Billions in Europe alone are given yearly to practical cybersecurity solutions. But what if we wanted, for once, to spend 2 cents in understanding the problem? After all, what is a cybersecure system? Let’s assume that a cybersecure system can be found in our reality, it’s like a very shy animal in a vast and intricate forest where all animals look similar. So, we know its name (cybersecure system) and… an expert reaches us and says: </p><p><em>Expert:</em> I know what a cybersecure animal looks like, we experts have a description of it.The cybersecure animal is brown! It is necessarily brown. </p><p><em>Us:</em> Really?! Have you ever seen it?  </p><p><em>Expert:</em> No, but if it wasn’t brown, it wouldn’t be brown. </p><p><em>Us:</em> Ooook, I’m really confused, what’s your problem again?  </p><p><em>Expert:</em> No! Listen to me! It’s like cybersecurity properties. A cybersecure system must be confidential otherwise it wouldn’t be! it must be brownnnn! </p><p><em>Us:</em> What the… why?! Why should I care about confidentiality or being brown? I just want a secure system!  </p><p><em>Expert:</em> It also must be 21 cm tall!  </p><p><em>Us:</em> Again?!?!  </p><p><em>Expert:</em> It’s like integrity, otherwi… </p><p>We look at the expert and something horrible happened! He has become a practical man. Suddenly, everyone is a practical man. There are no scientists around us, no philosophers, no professors, no ideas… everything is a practical solution for a practical problem in a world of dark practical men. And this is where we leave the practical expert (or, as we call him today, a cybersecurity researcher). They really sound smart at first, they are researchers, aren’t they? They are supposed to tell us the properties to prevent insecurities but, it turns out, they are just searching for insecurities and then mitigating them with ad-hoc properties; they are… searchers! </p><p>Still, we have nothing but the name of an animal (cybersecure) that doesn’t want to be found. It’s probably brown and 21cm tall, like any other animal in our forest. Finally, we stop searching for that animal, it seems impossible to find it. Let’s have a coffee and read a book, relax, and go with the flow. </p><h2 id="The-Evolution-of-the-Practical-Man"><a href="#The-Evolution-of-the-Practical-Man" class="headerlink" title="The Evolution of the Practical Man"></a>The Evolution of the Practical Man</h2><p>Days passed, then weeks, and months. We almost forgot about that weird cybersecure animal. We spent our time in understanding science and its philosophical aspects and, weirdly enough, it seems that the practical approach (of understanding new concepts out of the experience) is not the only way and, maybe, not the best or not even the right way. And suddenly, we think back to the cybersecure animal… could it be that… we made a terrible methodological error? So, we go back to the practical expert. </p><p><em>Us:</em> I was wondering… maybe… we could try to… start from some pure form of sensible intuition, such as space, and reason exclusively analytically, in the abstract, to formulate a sort of transcendental view of a cybersecure system. Sounds fun, right? </p><p><em>Expert:</em> Did you mean the CIA-triad? </p><p><em>Us:</em> What!? No, I don’t care abo… hufff… I mean, we should reason abstractly and search in this abstraction the concepts or properties that allow us to predict a certain phenomenon. We should not induce universal properties from experience or empirical experiments.  </p><p><em>Expert:</em> What do you think I’m doing?! I’m the expert! I abstract, I create… You and your mumbo jumbo, out of my expertise!  </p><p><em>Us:</em> No, wait, I didn’t express myself. Look, a hacker was altering my messages and I changed my system so that the hacker couldn’t change them anymore. But then he found another way to piss me off, and I found another way to block him and this went on and on and on… So, I thought, the hacker wasn’t doing anything wrong, he was just using the system. I now have a skeptic approach to life, there’s no right nor wrong. </p><p><em>Expert:</em> Are you insane? Do you want to let hackers do what they please, steal money, information and… </p><p><em>Us:</em> No no no… I understand why we believe hacker’s behaviors are wrong sometimes but, they aren’t technically doing something which is against what the systems allow them to do. We always fixed the system, not the hacker, he kept doing what he liked. So, it seems that a system is idealized as a set of behaviors (what the system is supposed to do) and realized with another (often mostly inclusive) set of behaviors (what the system actually does). </p><p><em>Expert:</em> What I hear is mumbo jumbo, stop thinking and start solving problems or fuck off that way! </p><p>Sadly, we move away from the expert and from their world of practicality. In science, abstract theories are tested against what they predict; we want a cybersecurity theory general enough so that we can empirically test it regardless of its domain of application. A theory that can be used to predict the cybersecurity of a system or all its insecurities so that attacks, at least, won’t come as a surprise.  </p><p>There must be another land, another realm where we can find the cybersecure animal. Maybe, when we find the cybersecure animal we can squeeze it to prepare a potion, something that cures the practical experts from their practicality. </p><p><strong>End of first act.</strong></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./neon-fish.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;https://www.neon-light.net/proddetail.php?prod=nl-107461-clown-fish-neon-sign&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;image-captio</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="cybersecurity" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/cybersecurity/"/>
    
    <category term="cyber-security" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/cyber-security/"/>
    
    <category term="cyber" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/cyber/"/>
    
    <category term="security" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/security/"/>
    
    <category term="sec" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/sec/"/>
    
    <category term="knowledgezero" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/knowledgezero/"/>
    
    <category term="blog" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/blog/"/>
    
    <category term="science" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/science/"/>
    
    <category term="practical-man" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/practical-man/"/>
    
    <category term="philosophy" scheme="https://www.knowledgezero.com/tags/philosophy/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
